<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Responsi 1 Mobile (H1D023114)</string>

    <!-- Nama Klub -->
    <string name="club_name">RC Celta de Vigo</string>

    <!-- Deskripsi Singkat Klub -->
    <string name="halaman_utama">
    Real Club Celta de Vigo, commonly known as Celta Vigo, is a Spanish professional football club based in Vigo, Galicia.\n
    Founded in 1923, the team plays its home matches at the Balaídos Stadium.\n
    Known for their sky blue jerseys, Celta is admired for its passionate fanbase and attacking style of play.
    </string>

    <!-- Label Tombol -->
    <string name="btn_history">Club History</string>
    <string name="btn_coach">Head Coach</string>
    <string name="btn_squad">Team Squad</string>
    <string name="back">Kembali</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- Sejarah Klub -->
    <string name="history_celta">
    Real Club Celta de Vigo was founded on 23 August 1923, as a result of the merger between two pioneer clubs of Vigo: Real Vigo Sporting and Real Fortuna de Vigo.\n\n
    Since then, Celta has held a special place in Galician football, embracing the region’s cultural identity and sporting ambition.\n\n
    From the early years, Celta established their home at the Estadio de Balaídos, inaugurated in December 1928.\n
    The club adopted the sky-blue and white colours in tribute to the Galician flag, capturing the regional pride that continues to define the team’s spirit.\n\n
    The 1940s and 1950s marked an era of perseverance for the club: Celta strived to cement themselves in Spain’s top leagues, battled relegations and earned promotions, and gradually built a legacy of competitive resilience.\n
    Despite never having won Spain’s two largest honours, the team became known for its entertaining attacking style and passionate fan base.\n\n
    In the 1990s and early 2000s, Celta entered a “golden” phase often dubbed “Euro Celta”, as the club competed regularly in European competitions, including the UEFA Intertoto Cup and UEFA Europa League.\n
    This period elevated the club’s profile, brought memorable nights in continental football and shaped the modern identity of the team.\n\n
    One of Celta’s greatest strengths has been its commitment to youth and talent development.\n
    Players like Iago Aspas emerged from the region’s footballing tradition and became symbols of the club’s values: loyalty, hard work, and flair.\n\n
    Off the pitch, Celta’s fan base in Vigo and throughout Galicia is among the most dedicated in Spain.\n
    The club, often referred to as “Os Celestes”, reflects its community’s pride, cultural roots, and resilient character.\n
    While major trophies have eluded them, the bond with supporters and the sense of identity has kept the club’s legacy thriving.\n\n
    In recent years, the club has focused on consolidating its place in the top-flight of Spanish football (La Liga), modernising the Balaídos stadium, investing in infrastructure, and preparing for future challenges.\n
    The journey of Celta de Vigo is not defined only by silverware, but by its story of regional pride, footballing passion, and continuous striving.\n\n
    As Celta approaches each new season, the legacy of over a century of football remains, rooted in Vigo and Galicia, driven by ambition and respect for its origins.\n
    The sky-blue jersey stands as a symbol — not just of a club, but of a community’s dream made real on the football field.
    </string>
</resources>
